<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
<SetOne>
<Stamp>
	<Title>Penny Black</Title>
	<Price>$3,000.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1840</Year>
	<Country>Great Britain </Country>
	<FaceValue>1 penny</FaceValue>
	<Description>The first stamp in the world! Most valued if it's unused. Produced in Great Britain on 1 May 1840 and has a picture of Queen Victoria. It's face value at its time was 1 penny (UK).</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>Hawaii Missionary Stamps</Title>
	<Price>$100,000.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1851</Year>
	<Country>Hawaii</Country>
	<FaceValue>2 cents</FaceValue>
	<Description>The first set of stamps in Hawaii. Called missionary because it was mostly used by missionaries when it was produced in 1851. It's face value at its time was 2 cents.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>1962 Dag Hammarskjold "Error Stamp"</Title>
	<Price>Cost Depends on Quality</Price>
	<Year>1962</Year>
	<Country>United States</Country>
	<FaceValue>4 Cents</FaceValue>
	<Description>Stamps similar to this exist, but this is unique because of the error made in 2 of its sheets in 1962, U.S. (the yellow background was inverted).</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>The U.S. "Inverted Airmail" Stamp</Title>
	<Price> $977,500.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1918</Year>
	<Country>United States</Country>
	<FaceValue>24 Cents</FaceValue>
	<Description>These stamps are unique because only the airplane part was accidentally printed upside-down, giving its uniqueness. Its face value is 24 cents.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>British Guiana 1-cent Magenta Stamp</Title>
	<Price>$9,480,000.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1856</Year>
	<Country>Great Britain</Country>
	<FaceValue>1 Cent</FaceValue>
	<Description>This stamp was limited to British Guinea in 1856 for newspapers, and was only issued in limited quantity. The auction rate of this stamp drastically rose when it was found that there was only one of it left in the world.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>Treskilling Yellow Stamp</Title>
	<Price>$2.88 million Swiss Franc </Price>
	<Year>1855</Year>
	<Country>Sweden</Country>
	<FaceValue>3 Swedish Skilling</FaceValue>
	<Description>The most expensive collector stamps! It is also known for its mistaken printing: usually in green color, only few exist in yellow color. Face value is 3 Swedish Skilling.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>The Two Penny Blue Stamps</Title>
	<Price>1 Million Euro</Price>
	<Year>1840</Year>
	<Country>Great Britain</Country>
	<FaceValue>2 Pence</FaceValue>
	<Description>This stamp bears the picture of Queen Victoria and were the world's second official stamp. Most valued because its original printing plates were destroyed and were not created after the first set.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>The New Brunswick Stamps</Title>
	<Price>£6,000 (with gum)</Price>
	<Year>1859</Year>
	<Country>Canada</Country>
	<FaceValue>5 Cents</FaceValue>
	<Description>This is the most ironic collector's stamp because General Connell used his portrait for stamps, but was denounced by the public for his negative reputation in politics. That's what made this stamp controversial.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>The U.S. "Farley's Follies" Stamps</Title>
	<Price>$0.30 (mint condition)</Price>
	<Year>1935</Year>
	<Country>United States</Country>
	<FaceValue>3 Cents</FaceValue>
	<Description>A set of commemorative stamps were given to the friends of Postmaster General James A. Farley, including one of which was for President Franklin D. Roosevelt. But the public protested to release and reprint the stamps for collection, that's why its unique but inexpensive.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>Red Mercury Stamp</Title>
	<Price>$40,000.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1856</Year>
	<Country>Austria</Country>
	<FaceValue>6kr - 30 centesimi</FaceValue>
	<Description>Created as a postage on newspapers, this stamp depicts the face of a Roman God and was printed in three colors: red, yellow, and blue. But the red ones were quickly replaced (in 1858), making them rare.</Description>
</Stamp>
<Stamp>
	<Title>Inverted Swan Stamp</Title>
	<Price>$35,000.00 - $80,000.00 USD</Price>
	<Year>1855</Year>
	<Country>Western Australia</Country>
	<FaceValue>4 Pence</FaceValue>
	<Description>One of the world's first inverted stamp errors; this specific stamp has an inverted image of a Black Swan, which is a symbol for the Australian Continent .Only 15 mint conditioned stamps survived to the present.</Description>
</Stamp>
</SetOne> 
